

ANNE-MARIE WYNNE

WEB & UX DESIGN

PROFILE

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Residency Auckland - NZ Citizen

Email a.wynne@xtra.co.nz

Phone 021 46 2013

Portfolio www.annemarie.me

Instagram annemarie.design

Pinterest AnnMarieDesign

Facebook ReturnToEdenChildrensBoutique annemarie24.design I am a passionate designer in many different fields and with the growth of technology I have been able to extend my skills and natural ability into that of web and UX design.

I am always excited to begin a new project - to work with a client taking a project from the initial concept through to delivering and implementing a product that is beyond expectations of both the client and the user. This is established with exceptional communication skills, understanding frustrations as well as the desired outcomes. researching, testing the prototype, problem solving and ultimately developing a final product that is simple with an aesthetically designed user interface and a high level of usability.

As well as strong customer and personable skills I am a highly motivated team player. I look forward to employment in a supportive environment where I can contribute and further develop my skills.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- UX & UI Design
- Usability Protocols
- Prototyping
- Persona Creation
- Information Architecture (IA)
- Photoshop/Illustrator/XD
- Design
- Lean Agile
- Scrum/Sprint
- Use Cases
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- SASS
- Git Hub
- Sublime
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Shopify
- Wordpress

EXPOSURE TO

- JavaScript/jQuery
- Node.js
- Php

EDUCATION

Feb 2017 - Present Yoobee School of Design

Diploma of Web and UX Design

Web & UX design along with programming skills as well as all other skills according to core competencies noted here

Feb 2016 - Jun 2016 Tauranga Victim Support Training

Tauranga Police Station

Full Victim Support Training including a Certificate of Completion for training in QPR Suicide Screening Course

Feb 2011 Whitecliffe School of Art and Design

Pattern Drafting for Fashion

One week full time Summer School - pattern drafting from body measurements and construction of test

garment to further my business goals

2010 Private Sewing Lessons

One on one sewing and garment construction lessons with a professional Dressmaker in Hamilton to build my own

business

2008 Photography Institute New Zealand

Professional Photography Course

2000-2002 The University of Auckland

BNurs - Bachelor of Nursing

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Research & Analytical Skills
- Ability to engage with clients and build a rapport
- Excellent Communication Skills
- Willingness to learn constantly
- Business centered and people focussed
- Enjoy working with others and autonomously
- Enjoy a challenge
- Enjoy problem solving
- Proactive
- Aware of own limitations and when to seek assistance
- Able to adapt to new surroundings, people and procedures easily
- Professional and discrete
- Able to maintain attention to detail and high standards while still meeting deadlines
- Social Media Strategies

INTERESTS

- Researching UX relevant material
- Designing and creating using a range of different media
- Photoshop
- Photography
- Instagram
- Journaling
- Paddleboarding
- Knitting my own designs
- Sewing my own designs
- Gardening
- Interior work in my home
- Skiing
- Bike Riding
- Movies with my partner
- Family, friends and my cats

WORK EXPERIENCE

2010 - 2016

Return To Eden Children's Boutique Sole Trader of own eCommerce Business

Designer, creator and owner of a Child's high end clothing brand – Return To Eden

- Management and maintenance of a high end eCommerce website designed by Zeald. This includes photographing and loading stock items, written information, placement of pages, images and layout.
- Designing email campaigns using Mailchimp and executing these
- Setting up a Shopify site the overall design, working on the graphics, product loading and descriptions, all copywriting, working with apps that are built for the Shopify framework, some coding
- Managing Google Analytics
- Marketing the business through Social Media via Facebook, Instagram and Twitter
- Developed Photography and Photoshop skills
- Photography work

2014 - 2016

eChic Website Designers Contract Web Designer

- Web design work for eChic using the Shopify Platform
- Australian based, however I worked remotely from New Zealand
- The company moved to New Zealand so was able to meet with New Zealand clients face to face
- Client management through the complete design process via Skype, phone and email

2008 - 2012

Project Network Group Limited Office and Accounts Manager

- Office Manager
- Payroll
- Dealing with Government Agencies
- Ensuring Contractors and Contractee are fulfilled
- GST/Payee
- Implementing office structures and procedures

2008 - 2009

Waitemata District Health Board Contract Office Administrator - North Shore Hospital

- Casual pool for relief work as needed (this proved to be daily/full time)
- Personal Assistant
- Leader of booking the casual staff while permanent leader was on leave
- Bookings at the Diabetes Clinic (full time for 3 months with the offer of a full time permanent placement)
- Clerical
- Reception
- Telephone contact with patients
- Knowledge of the Hospital computer system